Welcome back to our English listening practice.
مرحبا بعودتنا إلى ممارسة الاستماع للغة الإنجليزية.
How are you today?
كيف حالك اليوم؟
It's important for me to help you improve your skills.
من المهم بالنسبة لي أن أساعدك على تحسين مهاراتك.
So don't forget to share your feedback in the comments.
لذا لا تنس مشاركة ملاحظاتك في التعليقات.
Try to imagine yourself in real life situations
حاول أن تتخيل نفسك في مواقف الحياة الواقعية
where you need to speak English.
حيث تحتاج إلى التحدث بالإنجليزية.
Let's start with your first day at a hotel
لنبدأ بيومك الأول في فندق
in another country.
في بلد آخر.
You want to check in, ask questions, or request help.
تريد أن تتواصل معك، تسأل الأسئلة، أو تطلب المساعدة.
What would you say?
ماذا تقول؟
How would you understand the staff's answers?
كيف تفهم إجابات الموظفين؟
In many situations
في العديد من الحالات
you will need to ask for something.
ستحتاج إلى طلب شيء.
Imagine this with me.
تخيل هذا معي.
You are staying at a hotel in another country.
أنت تقيم في فندق في بلد آخر.
You feel nervous when talking to the receptionist.
تشعر بالتوتر عند التحدث إلى موظفة الاستقبال.
Maybe you don't understand what they said
ربما لا تفهم ما قالوه
or you aren't sure how to ask your question in English.
أو أنك لست متأكدا من كيفية طرح سؤالك بالإنجليزية.
It can feel stressful, but don't worry.
قد تشعر بالتوتر، لكن لا تقلق.
In this video, you will learn how to check in
في هذا الفيديو، ستتعلم كيفية تسجيل الأمور
ask questions, and speak politely in English at a hotel
اطرح الأسئلة، وتحدث بأدب بالإنجليزية في فندق
I will speak slowly and clearly
سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح
so you can follow easily.
لذا يمكنك المتابعة بسهولة.
You can listen carefully
يمكنك الاستماع جيدا
and repeat after me if you want.
وكرر ورائي إذا أردت.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟